{"sid": "GBMAIUN9H5J4_main", "calc_equals_delay": 3, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 334465, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 334465, "question": "16+786", "correct_answer": 802, "events": [["submit", 342089]], "time_left_end": "293", "answered_time": 342089, "user_answer": "802", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "293", "question_time_start": 342089, "question": "23+37", "correct_answer": 60, "events": [["calc_2", 343920], ["calc_3", 344205], ["calc_+", 345719], ["calc_3", 346152], ["calc_7", 346951], ["calc_=", 347684], ["submit", 355610]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "279", "answered_time": 355610, "user_answer": "60", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "279", "question_time_start": 355610, "question": "9+3+13", "correct_answer": 25, "events": [["submit", 361888]], "time_left_end": "273", "answered_time": 361888, "user_answer": "25", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "273", "question_time_start": 361888, "question": "3+44+28", "correct_answer": 75, "events": [["submit", 367883]], "time_left_end": "267", "answered_time": 367883, "user_answer": "75", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "267", "question_time_start": 367883, "question": "4+3+8+98", "correct_answer": 113, "events": [["calc_4", 370830], ["calc_+", 371413], ["calc_3", 371913], ["calc_+", 372729], ["calc_8", 373945], ["calc_+", 374527], ["calc_9", 375193], ["calc_8", 375544], ["calc_=", 376242], ["submit", 381521]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "253", "answered_time": 381521, "user_answer": "113", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "253", "question_time_start": 381521, "question": "3+7+4+24", "correct_answer": 38, "events": [["submit", 389198]], "time_left_end": "246", "answered_time": 389198, "user_answer": "38", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "246", "question_time_start": 389198, "question": "76+47", "correct_answer": 123, "events": [["submit", 395093]], "time_left_end": "240", "answered_time": 395093, "user_answer": "123", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "240", "question_time_start": 395093, "question": "7+3+7+68", "correct_answer": 85, "events": [["submit", 402103]], "time_left_end": "233", "answered_time": 402103, "user_answer": "85", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "233", "question_time_start": 402103, "question": "3+79+88", "correct_answer": 170, "events": [["submit", 408980]], "time_left_end": "226", "answered_time": 408980, "user_answer": "170", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "226", "question_time_start": 408981, "question": "7+6+99", "correct_answer": 112, "events": [["submit", 415025]], "time_left_end": "220", "answered_time": 415025, "user_answer": "224", "user_correct": "False", "score": "8"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 415025, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "220", "question_time_start": 415025, "question": "23+44", "correct_answer": 67, "events": [["submit", 422002]], "time_left_end": "213", "answered_time": 422002, "user_answer": "67", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "213", "question_time_start": 422002, "question": "4+9+47", "correct_answer": 60, "events": [["submit", 429562]], "time_left_end": "205", "answered_time": 429562, "user_answer": "60", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "205", "question_time_start": 429562, "question": "93+369", "correct_answer": 462, "events": [["submit", 437872]], "time_left_end": "197", "answered_time": 437872, "user_answer": "462", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "197", "question_time_start": 437872, "question": "4+4+4+87", "correct_answer": 99, "events": [["calc_1", 440037], ["calc_2", 440386], ["calc_+", 440921], ["calc_8", 441502], ["calc_7", 441851], ["calc_=", 442617], ["submit", 447963]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "187", "answered_time": 447963, "user_answer": "99", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "187", "question_time_start": 447963, "question": "88+43", "correct_answer": 131, "events": [["submit", 453475]], "time_left_end": "181", "answered_time": 453475, "user_answer": "131", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "181", "question_time_start": 453475, "question": "3+29+69", "correct_answer": 101, "events": [["submit", 459503]], "time_left_end": "175", "answered_time": 459503, "user_answer": "101", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "175", "question_time_start": 459503, "question": "8+7+7+39", "correct_answer": 61, "events": [["submit", 465697]], "time_left_end": "169", "answered_time": 465697, "user_answer": "61", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "169", "question_time_start": 465698, "question": "9+38+83", "correct_answer": 130, "events": [["submit", 472560]], "time_left_end": "162", "answered_time": 472560, "user_answer": "130", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "162", "question_time_start": 472561, "question": "6+7+9+84", "correct_answer": 106, "events": [["submit", 479469]], "time_left_end": "155", "answered_time": 479469, "user_answer": "106", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "155", "question_time_start": 479469, "question": "9+4+18", "correct_answer": 31, "events": [["submit", 484968]], "time_left_end": "150", "answered_time": 484968, "user_answer": "31", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 484968, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "150", "question_time_start": 484968, "question": "3+3+3+67", "correct_answer": 76, "events": [["submit", 490542]], "time_left_end": "144", "answered_time": 490542, "user_answer": "76", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "144", "question_time_start": 490542, "question": "54+94", "correct_answer": 148, "events": [["submit", 496587]], "time_left_end": "138", "answered_time": 496587, "user_answer": "148", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "138", "question_time_start": 496587, "question": "7+3+68", "correct_answer": 78, "events": [["submit", 499085]], "time_left_end": "136", "answered_time": 499085, "user_answer": "78", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "136", "question_time_start": 499085, "question": "4+66+17", "correct_answer": 87, "events": [["submit", 501865]], "time_left_end": "133", "answered_time": 501865, "user_answer": "87", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "133", "question_time_start": 501866, "question": "3+7+9+68", "correct_answer": 87, "events": [["submit", 509059]], "time_left_end": "126", "answered_time": 509059, "user_answer": "87", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "126", "question_time_start": 509059, "question": "23+546", "correct_answer": 569, "events": [["submit", 515204]], "time_left_end": "120", "answered_time": 515204, "user_answer": "569", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "120", "question_time_start": 515204, "question": "8+6+9+83", "correct_answer": 106, "events": [["submit", 523313]], "time_left_end": "112", "answered_time": 523313, "user_answer": "106", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "112", "question_time_start": 523314, "question": "16+39", "correct_answer": 55, "events": [["submit", 529227]], "time_left_end": "106", "answered_time": 529227, "user_answer": "55", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "106", "question_time_start": 529227, "question": "6+57+93", "correct_answer": 156, "events": [["submit", 535436]], "time_left_end": "100", "answered_time": 535436, "user_answer": "156", "user_correct": "True", "score": "27"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "100", "question_time_start": 535437, "question": "6+3+66", "correct_answer": 75, "events": [["submit", 540199]], "time_left_end": "95", "answered_time": 540199, "user_answer": "75", "user_correct": "True", "score": "28"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 540199, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "95", "question_time_start": 540199, "question": "4+9+3+44", "correct_answer": 60, "events": [["submit", 546726]], "time_left_end": "88", "answered_time": 546726, "user_answer": "60", "user_correct": "True", "score": "29"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "88", "question_time_start": 546727, "question": "4+3+23", "correct_answer": 30, "events": [["submit", 549940]], "time_left_end": "85", "answered_time": 549940, "user_answer": "30", "user_correct": "True", "score": "30"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "85", "question_time_start": 549940, "question": "64+16", "correct_answer": 80, "events": [["submit", 552255]], "time_left_end": "83", "answered_time": 552255, "user_answer": "80", "user_correct": "True", "score": "31"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "83", "question_time_start": 552255, "question": "6+47+93", "correct_answer": 146, "events": [["submit", 559965]], "time_left_end": "75", "answered_time": 559965, "user_answer": "146", "user_correct": "True", "score": "32"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "75", "question_time_start": 559965, "question": "3+8+9+57", "correct_answer": 77, "events": [["submit", 566478]], "time_left_end": "68", "answered_time": 566478, "user_answer": "77", "user_correct": "True", "score": "33"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "68", "question_time_start": 566478, "question": "83+734", "correct_answer": 817, "events": [["submit", 572654]], "time_left_end": "62", "answered_time": 572654, "user_answer": "817", "user_correct": "True", "score": "34"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "62", "question_time_start": 572654, "question": "8+93+64", "correct_answer": 165, "events": [["submit", 578698]], "time_left_end": "56", "answered_time": 578698, "user_answer": "165", "user_correct": "True", "score": "35"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "56", "question_time_start": 578699, "question": "4+7+6+14", "correct_answer": 31, "events": [["submit", 584261]], "time_left_end": "51", "answered_time": 584261, "user_answer": "31", "user_correct": "True", "score": "36"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "51", "question_time_start": 584261, "question": "67+13", "correct_answer": 80, "events": [["submit", 586808]], "time_left_end": "48", "answered_time": 586808, "user_answer": "80", "user_correct": "True", "score": "37"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "48", "question_time_start": 586808, "question": "3+9+24", "correct_answer": 36, "events": [["submit", 592902]], "time_left_end": "42", "answered_time": 592902, "user_answer": "36", "user_correct": "True", "score": "38"}}}, "block_4": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 592903, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "42", "question_time_start": 592903, "question": "8+73+86", "correct_answer": 167, "events": [["submit", 600080]], "time_left_end": "35", "answered_time": 600080, "user_answer": "167", "user_correct": "True", "score": "39"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "35", "question_time_start": 600080, "question": "16+57", "correct_answer": 73, "events": [["submit", 605808]], "time_left_end": "29", "answered_time": 605808, "user_answer": "73", "user_correct": "True", "score": "40"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "29", "question_time_start": 605808, "question": "7+7+3+56", "correct_answer": 73, "events": [["submit", 613235]], "time_left_end": "22", "answered_time": 613235, "user_answer": "73", "user_correct": "True", "score": "41"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "22", "question_time_start": 613235, "question": "4+7+9+79", "correct_answer": 99, "events": [["submit", 619796]], "time_left_end": "15", "answered_time": 619796, "user_answer": "99", "user_correct": "True", "score": "42"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "15", "question_time_start": 619796, "question": "7+3+33", "correct_answer": 43, "events": [["submit", 622193]], "time_left_end": "13", "answered_time": 622193, "user_answer": "43", "user_correct": "True", "score": "43"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "13", "question_time_start": 622194, "question": "98+474", "correct_answer": 572, "events": [["submit", 628588]], "time_left_end": "6", "answered_time": 628588, "user_answer": "572", "user_correct": "True", "score": "44"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "6", "question_time_start": 628588, "question": "3+6+8+64", "correct_answer": 81, "events": []}}}}}